<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>The Witcher Trials (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.TheWitcherTrials</packageId>
  <author>Imoja</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/TheWitcherTrials</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Imojas mod:
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1535737342

- Added support for CE
- Added a certain medallion

Patch by Darkstar for Medival playthrough using the Apotechary mod:
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2071060903

Original artwork by: ib2grh8
New artwork by: Delta

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
	[tr]
		[td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
		[td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/TheWitcherTrials][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
Image created by 'alexnegrea' of DeviantArt. (https://www.deviantart.com/alexnegrea/)
(Please save your game FIRST. These operations unbalance vanilla pawns, and [spoiler]failed Trails of the Grasses[/spoiler] may kill your pawns.)

[h1]Update v2.0:[/h1]
v2.0 - [spoiler]C# implemented, Operations are sequential and require ingredients, white hair, witcher swords, and more.[/spoiler]


[h1]Introduction[/h1]	
This mod allows you to research the ancient Witcher trials and perform the procedures on your pawns. You are able to research:[list]
[*] The Trial of the Grasses: The first trial. The body is manipulated with herbs, toxins and poisons. This primarily affects the nervous system.
[*] The Trial of the Dreams: The second trial. The mutation of the eyes, hormones and bone marrow is performed.
[*] The Trial of the Elders: The final trial. Forgotton practices were once performed on the witchers. You too can uncover these secrets, and pay the price.[/list]


[h1]Good questions so far:[/h1][list]
[*]I have a big modlist, are there any compatability issues? - I sincerely doubt it, my mod only adds.
[*]Can I use this on a running savegame? - Knock yourself out, will be fine. Uninstalling is a different matter. 
[*]When I apply a new Trial, the old one disappears? - This is expected behaviour. Its easier to calculate the balance of the mod when only one Trial is being applied to the stats.
[/list]

[h1]Anticipated questions:[/h1][list]
[*]Q: My hair isnt white?! - 
	A: [spoiler]Keep going.[/spoiler]
[*]Q: These ingredients are unrealistic!/The research takes too long!/The costs are too damn high!
	A: [spoiler]Honestly? Witchers are overpowered, think of witchers as implanting every bionic. Now do you get it?[/spoiler]
[/list]

[h1]UNINSTALLING THIS MOD:[/h1][olist]
[*] Enable Dev Mode. (BUT I PERMANENTLY DISABLED IT!? - you've just learnt a valuable lesson.)
[*] Use 'Destroy' to delete any items made by my mod.
[*] Use 'Remove Hediff...' to disable the Trials bonuses on your affect pawns.
[*] Save your game, exit rimworld.[/olist]
Your save should now be clean.


Feedback encouraged.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]

</description>
</ModMetaData>